<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Database>
	<EnglishText>
		<!-- Player Distribution Option (Multiplayer Only) -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_PLAYER_DISTRIBUTION">
			<Text>Multiplayer Human Spawns</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_PLAYER_DISTRIBUTION_DESC">
			<Text>Multiplayer only. Controls how human players spawn relative to each other. Has no effect in single-player games (always uses Random).</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Distribution Mode 0: Clustered -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_DISTRIB_CLUSTERED">
			<Text>Clustered (Default)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_DISTRIB_CLUSTERED_DESC">
			<Text>Human players spawn on the same or nearby continents. Ideal for cooperative and team-based play. Maximizes distant lands for shared exploration.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Distribution Mode 1: Spread -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_DISTRIB_SPREAD">
			<Text>Spread</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_DISTRIB_SPREAD_DESC">
			<Text>Human players spawn on different continents for competitive play. Always preserves at least one continent as distant lands for the exploration race.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Distribution Mode 2: Random -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_DISTRIB_RANDOM">
			<Text>Random</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_DISTRIB_RANDOM_DESC">
			<Text>No special placement for humans. All players distributed proportionally by continent size. Maximum unpredictability.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Continent Count Option -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_CONTINENT_COUNT">
			<Text>Continent Count</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_CONTINENT_COUNT_DESC">
			<Text>Controls how many continents are generated. Affects gameplay pacing, exploration dynamics, and player density per landmass. At least one continent is always reserved as Distant Lands.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Continent Count 0: Few -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_CONT_FEW">
			<Text>Few (2-4)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_CONT_FEW_DESC">
			<Text>Generates 2-4 large continents on all map sizes. More players share each landmass, emphasizing land-based expansion and early conflict. Fewer Distant Lands to discover.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Continent Count 1: Many -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_CONT_MANY">
			<Text>Many (5+)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_CONT_MANY_DESC">
			<Text>Generates many smaller continents. Scales with map size: Tiny 5-6, Small 5-7, Standard 5-8, Large 5-9, Huge 5-10. Players spread across landmasses. Emphasizes naval exploration and island-hopping.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Continent Count 2: Random (Default) -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_CONT_RANDOM">
			<Text>Random (Default)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CPP_CONT_RANDOM_DESC">
			<Text>Continent count varies by map size: Tiny 2-5, Small 2-6, Standard 3-4, Large 4-7, Huge 5-8. Each game is different. Recommended for maximum replayability.</Text>
		</Row>
	</EnglishText>
</Database>
